{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arapa","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aša","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estitati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"esto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etiri","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrnaest","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"initi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ist","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"okolada","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ovjek","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uvati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ćevap","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"de","osnova2":"ko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"djevoj","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"doru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"doru","osnova2":"kovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"druga","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"hla","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ju","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kau","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kola","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljubi","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mjese","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nao","osnova2":"ale","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naran","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naran","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nau","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nave","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obi","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"ekivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pala","osnova2":"inka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"papu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"etak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"un","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"unalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"razli","osnova2":"it","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rje","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ruži","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sendvi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sestri","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sije","osnova2":"anj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"simpati","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sveu","osnova2":"ilište","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tr","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"era","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"erati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"velja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"anje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zna","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"brati","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"cvije","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ćevap","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"drve","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"du","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ga","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"i","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ispe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"iza","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kafi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"liš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mladi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mogu","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"no","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"obu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"odje","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"oti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pono","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"posje","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"povr","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"prolje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"re","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sino","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sje","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sljede","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"še","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tisu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"uop","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vra","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
